A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential records, Secretariat, Weekly Briefing Notes, Series 14 FA261
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Briefing Notes: Raw Materials, 1975 May 15 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Topics covered: U.S. Dependence for Resources, Metals, and Energy
- Briefing Notes: Healthcare, 1975 June 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Topics covered: National Health Expenditures and Financing, Health Status, Manpower and Facilities, Utilization
- Briefing Notes: Housing, 1975 June 11 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Topics Covered: Population and Housing, Changes in Regional Distribution of Housing, New Residential Construction Since 1965, Selected Housing Characteristics, Owners and Renters, Income and Cost of Housing
- Briefing Notes: Farm Spreads, 1975 July 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Topics Covered: Shares of the Market Basket, Farm Value, Marketing Spread and Retail Cost, Consumer's Bread Price, The Marketing Bill, Farm Income
- Briefing Notes: Imports of Critical Minerals, 1975 September 15 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Topics Covered: Algeria-Brazil, Canada- France, Gabon- Liberia, Malaysia- Peru, Republic of South Africa- Surinam, Thailand- Zaire
- Briefing Notes: The Social and Economic Status of the Black Population, 1975 September 22 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Topics Covered: Population, Family Structure and Growth, Education, Labor Force, Income, Health, Housing, Voter Participation, Crime
- Briefing Notes: Crime and Criminal Justice, 1975 October 10 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Topics Covered: Series: Incidence of Crimes, Police and Judicial Activities, Inmates of Penal Institutions, Expenditures for Criminal Justice
- Briefing Notes: State and Local Government Finances, 1976 February 27 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Topics Covered: Federal State and Local Government- Trends and Comparisons, State Government Finances, Local Government Finances, Appendix A State and Local Governmental General Revenue, Expenditures, and Indebtedness by State: 1967 ad 1974 (Per $1,00 Personal Income and Per Capita), Appendix B Definitions of Selected Terms